Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.eleven Mss.B.B61.inventory11
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents R
  - Romain, Lulu (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 5
  - Romains, Jules (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1940 July 18
  - Roman, C.V. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
  - Romeike, A. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 21
  - Romer, M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 2
    - To Boas, 1923 May 9
  - Romero, C. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 3
  - Ronchitti [?] (Box 76)
    - To Mrs. Ravizza, 1897 Feb. 8
      re: G. Ravené
  - Ronciore, C. de la (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 17
    - To Boas with enc.
      - (Birket-Smith & Gusinde, M.), 1933 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas with enc., 1933 Mar. 27
  - Rood, O.N. (Box 76)
    - To Dr. A. Jacobi, 1884 Nov. 30
      (cards of introduc. for F.B. in Washington)
    - To Dr. A. Jacobi, 1885 Jan. 30
  - Roos, C.F. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1931 May 15 and May 19
    - From Boas, 1931 May 21
    - From Boas, 1931 May 27
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 25; 2p
      - see reverse of Ebding, 1931 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1931 May 20
      enc. Clark, A.H. to Day, A.L.
      - Roos -- to Russell, H., 1931 May 19
      - Roos -- to Watson, E.C., 1931 May 20
    - To Boas, 1931 June 2
    - To Boas, 1931 June 15
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 9
      - enc. to Cattell, J., 1931 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1932 May 28
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 9
    - To A.A.A.S. Council, 1931 Sep. 25; 4p
    - To Cattell, J.M., 1931 Nov. 20
    - To Cattell, J.M., 1931 Nov. 14
    - To Elliott, D.S., 1931 Oct. 31
    - To Noyes, W.A., 1931 May 4
    - To Russell, H.N., 1931 May 20
    - To Ward, H.B., 1931 Nov. 14
    - To Watson, E.C., 1931 May 20
    - From Bowman, J.G., 1931 July 31
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 76)
    - From Boas re Santander, 1937 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano (Box 76)
    - From Boas (enc. with FB to Moley, R.C.), 1933 Mar. 17; 2pand
      - draft, 1939 July 31
        re: E. Browder case
      - (enc. with FB to Biddle, Francis), 1941 Nov. 12; 2p
    - From Boas (enc. with FB to Moley, R.C.), 1941 Nov. 12
    - To Boas (see EfrC3n, D.), 1937 Sep. 4
      see Columbia U. staff
    - To Boas (see EfrC3n, D.), 1938 Dec. 31
    - From Anon., 1939 Dec. 31
    - To Hinckley, W., 1936 Nov. 17
    - From Kraus, A.J., 1940 May 20
    - To Robert E. Lane, 1938 Dec. 14
      enc. 4 papers on aid to refugee students
    - From Ross, E.A., 1941 Sep. 15
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
  - Roosval, J. (Box 76)
    - To Boas re Born, W., 1934 Sep. 18
  - Root, Elihu (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1911 May 18; 6p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 23
    - To Boas, 1911 June 15
    - To McAneny, G., 1918 Mar. 27
  - Roper, R.C. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 19
  - Ropes, James Hardy (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 2p
  - Roquette-Pinto, E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10
  - Rosales, R.C. (Box 76)
    - To Am. Coun. Learned Societies, 1933 Aug. 11
  - Rosamond, M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 6
  - Rose, A. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 13; 2p
  - Rose, C. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1908 July 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 14; 2p
  - Rose, Ernestine (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1922 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 28
  - Roselius, Ludwig (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 27; 3p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 2p
  - Rosen, Al (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 2
    - To Boas, 1937 July 19
  - Rosen, J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 17
  - Rosen, J.F. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 19
  - Rosenau, M.J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 1
  - Rosenbach, A.S.W. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1933 June 22
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 1
  - Rosenbach, L.J. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1934 July 13
  - Rosenbaum (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 14
  - Rosenbaum, E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 27; 2p
  - Rosenberg, J.N. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 8
  - Rosenberg, Perry (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 4
  - Rosenberg, S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 25
  - Rosenblatt, Louise (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 6
  - Rosenblatt, Wm. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 6
  - Rosenblum, David (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 1
    - To Warburg, M.M., 1942 July 9
      - enc. with M.M., 1942 July 10
  - Rosenblum, G.A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 14; 2p
  - Rosenfeld, Kurt (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1942 May 4
    - From Boas, 1942 June 1
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1936Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1940 June 23
      - list of Germ. refugees, 1940 Dec. 31
      - Boenheim, F. cosigned
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1942 May 5
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 9; 2p
      - enc. KR letter to, 1942 Dec. 22
      - N.Y. Times Editor, 1942 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, E.P. Editor, 1942 Dec. 22
  - Rosenfeld, L. (Box 76)
    - To Szilard enc. with, 1933 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, E.P. from Liebowitz, B., 1933 May 4
    - To Szilard enc. with, 1933 May 2
    - To Boas, E.P. from Liebowitz, B., 1933 May 4
  - Rosensohn, M. (Box 76)
    - from Boas, 1924 May 27
  - Rosenstengel, Helen, 1924 May 27 (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 14; 2p
  - Rosenthal, Abraham - YMHA (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 24
  - Rosenthal, D. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 27
  - Rosenthal, J. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 12
  - Rosenthal, Leon (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 19
  - Rosenwald, Julius (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 18
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 19
    - From Billikopf, J., 1933 Nov. 8
  - Rosenwald, Wm. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 17
  - Rosenwasser, Harry (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 29
  - Rosenzweig, Gerald (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 8; 2p
  - Roses & Co. (Sucesores de) (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 16
  - Rosinski, B. (Box 76)
    - See FB open letter, 1930 July 10
  - Rosoff, Peter (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 19
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 19
    - To Durlach, T.M., 1937 July 13
  - Ross, Alan S.C. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 6; 3p
  - Ross, Denman, W. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1911 June 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 20; 4p
  - Ross, E.A., Chairman, ACLU (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 17; 2p
    - See FB to Carlson, A.J., 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1941 Sep. 5
    - To Roosevelt, F.D., 1941 Sep. 15
  - Ross, Elwood -- [not E.A. above] (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 26
  - Ross, Emory (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 3
  - Ross, F.A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1930 May 13
      - Negro migration, 1930 Dec. 31; 3p
      - Negro migration, 1930 Dec. 31; 2p
      - enc. with MacIver, R.M., 1930 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 30
  - Ross, Jacob M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 7
  - Rossauer, H.O. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 4p
  - Rosset, Chas. E., Swiss Consul Gen'l (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 22
  - Rossignol, J.E. de (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 16
  - Rostovtzeff, M. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 23
  - Roth (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 4
  - Roth, Karl (Box 76)
    - book rev. of Strzygowski, 1924 Mar.
  - Roth, Walter E. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1903 July 29
    - enc. with Herskovits, M.J., 1929 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 4
  - Rothe, Erich (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 12
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 17
    - From Anon., 1934 Aug. 10
  - Rothschild, Robert de (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 9; 2p
  - Rouge (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 19
  - Rouma, Georges (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 11
  - Roumain, Jacques (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 14
  - Rousseau, Jacques, Ass'n Can. Francaise (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 13
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1937 May 13
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 17
  - Rowe (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
  - Rowe, Floyd A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 31
  - Rowe, L.S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1930 May 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1930 May 3
  - Rowell, W.C. H.W. Wilson Co. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 10
  - Rowland, W. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1913 June 31
  - Roy, L.A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 July 29
  - Roy, M.M. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 31
  - Roy, S.C. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1921 May 13
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 20
  - Royal Anthropological Institute, Secretary (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7
  - Royal Bank of Canada, Prince RupertBranch (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 July 13
  - Royal Society of Canada (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1888 Sep. 8
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 19
  - Rubel, L.E., -- Underwood & Underwood (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1930 July 3
  - Rubens, Harry (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 4p
  - Rubenstein, Annette T. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 3
  - Rubenstein, Herman J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 12
    - From Boas, 1938 May 18
    - To Boas, 1938 May 11; 2p
  - Rubin de la Borbolla, Daniel F. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 5
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22
    - From Boas, 1939 June 26
    - From Boas, 1939 Aug. 2
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1939 June 29
    - To Boas, 1939 June 30
    - To Boas, 1939 July 2
    - To Boas, 1942 May 14
  - Rubinow, I.M. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 13
    - To Badman, T., enc., 1934 Oct. 23
    - To Badman, T., enc., 1935 Jan. 12
  - Rubio, Dario (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 12
    - To Boas, 1931 June 3
  - Rubner, Max (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 17
    - Paper on nutrition, see Seeliger, H., 1922 Feb. 20; 6p
  - Ruden, Elliott S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 15; 2p
  - Rudolf Eucken-Haus (Box 76)
  - Rudolf Eucken-Haus, Aufruf der Freunde (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1931 end
  - Ruedin (Box 76)
    - re: Kallmann, Franz, 1936 May 30
    - enc. with Kallmann, Franz, 1936 Oct. 26
  - Ruest, Anselm (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 14
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 20; 4p
      see also Samuel, Ernst
  - Rueter, Henry A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Rueter, W.G. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Rukeyser, M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20
  - Ruml, Beardsley (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 30; 3p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 17
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 16; 3p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1926 May 19
    - To Stang, F., 1926 June 11; 2p
  - Rummel, Georg (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 10
  - Rumsey, C.E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
  - Rundle, G.P. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 17
  - Rundle, Ltd. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2
  - Rune (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct 17; 2p
  - Runes, Dagobert D. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 11
  - Ruppert (Box 76)
    - From Boas
      - see FB to Cadman, S.P., 1933 May 29
  - Ruppin (Box 76)
    - from Zollschan, J., 1934 Apr. 7
      - enc. with Zollschan, J., 1934 Apr. 8
  - Russ, Miss (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 12
  - Russell, E.F. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 21
  - Russell, Frank (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 21
  - Russell, M.? (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1906 May 7
  - Russell, H.N. (Box 76)
    - From Roos, C.F., 1931 May 20
  - Russell, J.E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 2; 3p
    - From Boas, 1903 Mar. 16 and 1904 Feb. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 20
  - Russell, John M. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1939 June 27
  - Russell, Richard B. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 18
  - Russell, W.F. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 7
  - Russell, Wm. L., Inst. Intern. Ed. (Box 76)
    - Mimeo. letter, 1925 Feb. 19
  - Rust, Horatio N. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 22
  - Ruth
    See Benedict, Ruth Foster
  - R.W. Large Memorial Hosp. (Box 76)
    See Darby, Geo. E.
  - Ryan, G.J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 27
    - From Linville, H.R., 1929 Jan. 19
      - originally with H.R., 1929 Jan. 21
  - Ryan, W.C., Jr. (Box 76)
    - From Bronson, R.M., 1935 Sep. 18
      - enc. with Collier, J., 1935 Sep. 24
  - Ryce, L.C. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 17
  - Rydberg, P.A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1921 May 2
    - To Boas, 1907 June 28
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 22
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 28
  - Rygodas Ful?? J., 1923 May 24 (Box 76)